rapsio.com 2019-01-11

# PrivacyPolicy - Rapsio AdPortal

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains what information Mako Labs LLC, the owner of Rapsio (“Rapsio,” also referred to herein as “us,” “we,” or “our”) collects from individuals who visit the Rapsio.com website (the “Site”), and it explains how Rapsio uses and maintains this information. 

## Privacy Policy Changes

We reserve the right to update or modify the Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any changes to the Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on our Site, so please review it frequently. The Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the Site and not to information collected or obtained from other sources.

## Information Collected

We collect two (2) kinds of information through the Site:

  1. Personally-Identifiable Information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name and email address (“PII”). We only collect PII when you have contacted us directly (see “Collection of Personally-Identifiable Information” below).
  2. Non personally-identifiable information (“NPII”) collected and stored automatically by many websites. This includes information about your Internet service provider, operating system, browser type, geographic location and pages viewed on the Site. Although this information is related to you, we do not associate it with your PII and it cannot be linked to you personally.

If you do not want your information to be collected and used per the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should not access the Site.

## Personally-Identifiable Information (PII)

PII is collected by the Site only when you provide it to us when:

  * You communicate with us via email. We ask that you provide us your name, email address and phone number so that we can send you a response.
  * You visit a sign up page for ads, apps, and games, and you are requested to submit (i) your name, (ii) your company name, (iii) your address, (iv) a username and password, (v) your email address, and (vi) information that Rapsio may request from time to time as indicated on the sign up page.

If you do not want us to collect your PII or to use and share your PII, you should NOT provide it to us through any of the Site features described above. By providing us with your PII through use of these features, you are authorizing our use and sharing of your PII as described in this Privacy Policy and any subsequent revisions to it.

We will retain your information for as long as needed to provide you services, or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolution of disputes and enforcement of our agreements. You may update, correct, amend or request to remove your PII from our systems by emailing us [support@rapsio.com](mailto:support@rapsio.com).

## Child Privacy

The Site and all information, content and materials contained on the Site (in any form or media, the “Site Materials”) are neither intended for, nor directed to, nor to be accessed by, persons under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under 13 years old. We cannot and will not independently verify that all those who use the Site are at least 13 years of age but we will remove from our files any PII of anyone we discover to be under 13 years old.

## Use and Sharing of Personally-Identifiable Information

We reserve the right to use PII: (i) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided as stated above; (ii) for the purposes disclosed at the time such information is provided; or (iii) as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

We do not share, sell or trade any of your PII with any third parties other than described herein. We may share your PII with our parent company and companies owned by our parent company (collectively "Related Entities"). Neither we nor our Related Entities contribute to or participate in cooperative databases, which give other companies access to your PII.

We and our Related Entities may provide access to your PII when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site, to limit our legal liability and to protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of other users or the public.

We and/or our Related Entities may also disclose your PII to outside companies and consultants that help bring you the services we offer. For example, we and our Related Entities may work with outside companies and consultants to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist in distributing e-mails; (c) assist with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone; and/or (g) provide other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential and maintaining our Site. We and our Related Entities require that these outside companies and consultants agree to keep confidential all information we share with them, and use the information only to perform their obligations to us.

In addition, if we or our Related Entities go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your PII will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by a prominent notice on the Site of any such change in ownership or control of your PII. We also reserve the right to disclose PII as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

## Non Personally-Identifiable Information (NPII)

As with many websites, when you visit our Site, it automatically gathers certain NPII based on your computer information and stores it in log files. This type of technical/statistical information is used to customize your experience on the Site, to help us improve the quality of the Site and to make your visits to the Site easy and convenient. The Site also collects your IP address to help diagnose problems with the Site server and for Site administration purposes.

We share NPII with our business partners to customize the services they and we provide to you. And, we may also disclose any NPII collected from you through the Site to: (i) comply with applicable laws, (ii) respond to governmental inquiries, (iii) comply with valid legal process, or (iv) protect our rights and property or that of or our users.

## Cookies

A Cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies can’t be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

We use cookies to collect aggregate Internet traffic statistics and better understand our users. This allows us to enhance your experience on the Site. This data collected may include user preferences and product utilization information such as number of visitors, features used, average time spent on pages and other information which help us determine which features are working effectively and are most important to you.

You can set your browser to reject cookies from the Site or to notify you when any website tries to put a cookie in your browser. However, if you choose to decline cookies in this manner, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site and this may affect your ability to use some of the services at the Site. We do not tie any PII to the cookies that we set.

## Third Party Cookies

Because we do not have access or control over these cookies, this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by our third party advertisers as well as third party ad servers. These third parties use session ID cookies to gather anonymous information.

## Links from the Site

The Site may provide links to the websites of our business partners. If you link to any of these third party web sites, this Privacy Policy will not apply to your use of those sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these web sites, including their privacy policies. We shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these sites. Any inquiries you have concerning the use of PII by a third party must be communicated to that third party and not to us.

## Security

We have implemented physical, technical and administrative security measures to protect Information from unauthorized access and improper use. We keep information on servers protected by firewalls and located in a physically secure facility. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any connection to the Site or information transmitted to us or to the Site will be at your own risk.

## Question and Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about the Site or the Privacy Policy or its implementation, please email us at [support@rapsio.com](mailto:support@rapsio.com).

Effective: July 23, 2014, as amended December 10, 2018
